Guide to the William Walker Whitehall Johnston Photograph Album of Wales, the West Indies, and the 1st West India Regiment
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photograph Album, circa 1858-1865; Series I
  - Album Page 73. Recto, top: Harbour Street in Kingston, Jamaica; image includes storefronts for the Scott's Clothing Warehouse; Alexander Berry, cabinet maker; Maurice Farmer and Brother; Frederick Alexander and Company; and S. Laraque, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Album Page 73. Recto, bottom: Three black men standing in front of a carriage that holds another black man in front of the Cosmopolitan Gallery in Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Album Page 73. Verso: Barracks at Fort Charlotte in Nassau, New Providence, circa 1860 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Album Page 74. Recto: Marine Square and Almond Walk in Port of Spain, Trinidad; image shows buildings, promenade, and fountain, circa 1860 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Album Page 75. Verso: Monument to Ferdinand VII of Spain, sculpted by Antonio Solá in 1834, and the Palacio de los Capitanes Generales in the Plaza de Armas, Havana, Cuba, circa 1860 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Album Page 76. Recto: View from El Templete of the monument to Ferdinand VII of Spain, sculpted by Antonio Solá in 1834, and the Palacio de los Capitanes Generales in the Plaza de Armas, Havana, Cuba, circa 1860 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Album Page 76. Verso: El Templete in the Plaza de Armas, Havana, Cuba, circa 1860 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Album Page 77. Recto: Barracks at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Album Page 78. Recto: Barracks at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Album Page 79. Recto: Ruins of Neath Abbey in Neath, Wales, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Album Page 80. Recto: Neath from the house at Cadoxton Lodge Estate, Cadoxton-juxta-Neath, Wales, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Same image appears on Album Page 28, recto
  - Album Page 81. Recto: House and Garden of Park Lodge, London, England, with a young man seated in the garden and a boy in the doorway, identified as Walter Mowbray Johnston (1842-1919) and Francis Hope Johnston (died 1874), 1858 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    Same image appears on Album Page 11, recto.
  - Album Page 82. Recto: House in the distance on a hill, probably Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Album Page 83. Recto: Informal group portrait of seventeen officers dressed in fatigue battle uniforms, probably in front of barracks at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica; William Walker Whitehall Johnston posed standing at far left, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Album Page 84. Recto: Informal group portrait of fourteen non-commissioned black officers in 1st West India Regiment at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Album Page 85. Recto: Informal group portrait of twenty non-commissioned officers and enlisted men, black and white, in 1st West India Regiment at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Same image appears on Album Page 86, recto
  - Album Page 86. Recto: Informal group portrait of twenty non-commissioned officers and enlisted men, black and white, in 1st West India Regiment at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Same image appears on Album Page 85, recto
  - Album Page 87. Recto: Group portrait of twenty-one non-commissioned officers and enlisted men, black and white, in 1st West India Regiment in formation with field artillery at Up-Park Camp, Kingston, Jamaica, circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 85)